(由TurboScribe轉錄。 升級到無限以移除此訊息。) Hey, guys.
（由TurboScribe負責。升級到無限以刪除此訊息。）嘿，夥計們。
Hey.
嘿。
So, what do you think?
那麼，你覺得怎麼樣？
About what?
關於什麼？
What?
什麼？
Are you kidding?
你在開玩笑吧？
Okay, I'll give you a hint, I'll give you a hint.
好吧，我給你一個提示，我給你一個提示。
Eyes.
眼睛。
No, no.
不，不。
Your eyes.
你的眼睛。
No.
不。
Chandler's eyes.
錢德勒的眼睛。
I got glasses.
我戴了眼鏡。
You always had glasses.
你一直都戴著眼鏡。
No, I didn't.
不，我沒有。
Are you sure?
你確定嗎？
Didn't you used to have a pair?
你以前不是有一雙嗎？
They were really round and burgundy and they made you look kind of...
它們真的很圓，呈酒紅色，讓你看起來有點…
Feminine.
女性化。
Yes.
是的。
No.
不。
Sweetie, I think the glasses look great.
親愛的，我覺得這副眼鏡很好看。
They make you look really sexy.
它們讓你看起來非常性感。
Really?
真的嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
You didn't think I used to wear glasses, right?
你以為我以前不戴眼鏡吧？
Of course.
當然。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
I'll be there for you When the rain starts to pour I'll be
我會在你身邊當雨開始傾盆而下時我會在
there for you Like I've been there before I'll be there for you
就像我以前來過一樣，我會在你身邊
So there for you So
所以有你的所以
what do you guys want for an engagement present?
你們想要什麼訂婚禮物？
That's okay, Pheebs.
沒關係，菲比。
We're not having a party or anything, so you don't have to get
我們沒有舉辦派對或其他任何活動，所以你不必參加
it If someone wants to give us a present, we don't want to
如果有人想送我們禮物，我們不想
deprive them of that joy Oh, you know what you should get them?
剝奪他們的那種快樂哦，你知道你該給他們什麼嗎？
One of those little portable CD players Oh, I already have one Not
那些小型行動式 CD 播放器之一 哦，我已經有一個 沒有
unless someone borrowed it and left it at the gynecologist Yeah, and by
除非有人藉用它並把它留在婦科醫生處 是的，然後
someone, she means Joey Hey, I know what I want What we want,
某人，她指的是喬伊 嘿，我知道我想要什麼 我們想要什麼，
honey No, no, you don't want this I want to have your grandmother's
親愛的，不，不，你不要這個，我想要你祖母的
cookie recipe You mean the chocolate chip cookie recipe?
餅乾食譜 你是說巧克力餅乾食譜嗎？
Uh-huh, yeah You mean the one that my grandmother made me swear
嗯嗯，是的，你是說我祖母要我發誓的那個
on her deathbed that I would never let out of our family?
在她臨終前我永遠不會讓她離開我們的家庭？
Giant people say the craziest things I've wanted it for years.
巨人說出了我多年來一直想要的最瘋狂的話。
I'm just going to make cookies for my children Break my heart Oh,
我只是要為我的孩子們做餅乾讓我心碎哦，
all right Okay, I'm going to be the mom who makes the world's
好吧，好吧，我要成為創造世界的媽媽
best chocolate chip cookies Our kids are going to be fat, aren't they?
最好的巧克力餅乾 我們的孩子會變胖，不是嗎？
Ahoy!
哎喲！
Hey, how's the boat?
嘿，船怎麼樣？
Great, I'm really getting into this sailing stuff Oh, so you finally took
太棒了，我真的很喜歡航海的東西哦，所以你終於接受了
it out of the marina, huh?
是從碼頭出來的吧？
Why would I do that?
我為什麼要這麼做？
It took three guys to get the thing in there Well, if you
三個人才把東西搬進去 好吧，如果你
don't sail your boat, what do you do on it?
不開船，你在上面做什麼？
That's great.
那太棒了。
It's a great place to just kind of sit, hang around, drink a
這是一個坐下來、閒逛、喝一杯的好地方
few beers, eat some chips Well, it's good that you finally have a
喝幾瓶啤酒，吃點薯條 好吧，很高興你終於擁有了
place to do that You know, Joey, I could teach you to sail
你知道，喬伊，我可以教你航海
if you want You could?
如果你願意的話可以嗎？
Yeah, I've been sailing my whole life When I was 15, my dad
是的，我一生都在航海 當我 15 歲的時候，我爸爸
bought me my own boat Your own boat?
給我買了我自己的船 你自己的船？
What?
什麼？
He was trying to cheer me up.
他試著讓我高興起來。
My pony was sick You
我的小馬病了 你
know what I was thinking?
知道我在想什麼嗎？
What?
什麼？
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
I just like to go like this Hey Chandler, what are you doing
我就是喜歡這樣 嘿錢德勒，你在做什麼
tonight?
今晚？
Uh, why?
呃，為什麼？
Do you have a lecture?
有講座嗎？
No, why?
不，為什麼？
Then free as a bird.
然後像小鳥一樣自由。
What's up?
這是怎麼回事？
Uh, my dad wants to know if you want to play racquetball with
呃，我爸爸想知道你是否想跟我一起打壁球
us Wow, that's great.
我們哇，太棒了。
Dad must really like you.
爸爸一定很喜歡你。
He doesn't ask just anyone to play Yeah, and he didn't really ask
他不要求任何人參加比賽 是的，他並沒有真正要求
for you.
為你。
He asked for Chauncey I assumed he meant you Well, did you correct
他問昌西 我以為他指的是你 嗯，你說對了嗎
him?
他？
No, I thought it would be more fun this way That is so
不，我以為這樣會更有趣 原來如此
cool.
涼爽的。
Maybe this is something you could do every week Yeah, or you could
也許這是你每週都可以做的事情 是的，或者你可以
sit with him on the front porch and make sure no one steals
和他一起坐在前廊，確保沒有人偷竊
the trash cans He does that every week too Oh, just so you
垃圾桶 他每週也這樣做 哦，只是為了讓你
know, you have to let him win.
知道，你必須讓他贏。
He hates to lose Oh, no problem.
他討厭失去哦，沒問題。
Maybe I'll play with my left hand You're not a lefty?
也許我會用左手玩你不是左撇子嗎？
Does anybody know me?
有人認識我嗎？
What's wrong, Phoebe?
怎麼了，菲比？
I just went to my old apartment to get you the cookie recipe
我剛去我的舊公寓給你餅乾食譜
and that stupid fire burned it up No!
那愚蠢的火把它燒毀了不！
Why didn't you make a copy and keep it in a fireproof box
為什麼不影印一份並儲存在防火盒裡
and keep it at least 100 yards away from the original?
並與原來保持至少100碼的距離？
Because I'm normal That was the one legacy my grandmother left me and
因為我很正常 那是我祖母留給我的唯一遺產
I know you wanted it as an engagement present We have to get
我知道你想要它作為訂婚禮物 我們必須得到
you an engagement present?
你有訂婚禮物嗎？
Don't worry about it, Phoebs No one got me an engagement present Okay,
別擔心，菲布斯沒有人送訂婚禮物好吧，
here.
這裡。
I don't have the recipe, but here I wish you health and happiness
我沒有食譜，但在這裡祝你健康快樂
An old cookie?
一塊舊餅乾？
This is what happens when you don't register for gifts I made a
這就是當你不註冊我製作的禮物時會發生的情況
batch and I froze it and this is the only one left We
一批，我把它冷凍起來，這是唯一剩下的我們
can't accept this Why not?
不能接受這個為什麼不行？
Because it's gross No, wait.
因為這太噁心了 不，等等。
I think I can figure out the recipe from this cookie I do
我想我可以從我做的這塊餅乾中找出食譜
stuff like this at work all the time Really?
工作上常有這樣的事情真的嗎？
Yeah, I think I can do it Oh, yay!
是的，我想我能做到，哦，耶！
Okay, Ross, we owe you a present Two!
好吧，羅斯，我們欠你一份禮物二！
I've been engaged twice!
我已經訂婚兩次了！
Look at this clown Just because he got a bigger boat, he thinks
看看這個小丑 他認為只是因為他有一艘更大的船
he can take up the whole river Get out of the way, jackass!
他可以佔據整條河 別擋道，混蛋！
Who names their boat Coast Guard, anyway?
到底是誰為他們的船命名的海岸警衛隊？
That is the Coast Guard What are they doing out here?
那是海岸警衛隊 他們在這裡做什麼？
The coast is all the way over there Joey, just ignore the boats,
喬伊那邊就是海岸，別理會那些船，
all right?
好的？
We're not finished with our lesson yet All right Okay, I'm just going
我們的課還沒上完 好吧 好吧 我先走了
to go over the basic points one more time Are you ready?
再複習一遍基本要點 你準備好了嗎？
Come on, Rach.
來吧，瑞秋。
Not again.
不會再有。
I got it, okay?
我明白了，好嗎？
Let's start sailing And I want to go over there where that boatload
讓我們開始航行吧我想去那艘船所在的地方
of girls is Yo-ho!
女孩們的最愛是喲呵！
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
Is that what you want to do?
這就是你想做的事嗎？
You want to go over and give a little shout-out to the
你想走過去大聲喊叫
old hot chicas, huh?
老辣妹，是嗎？
Okay Let's do that, Sailor Joe Quick question, though What's this called?
好的，讓我們開始吧，水手喬，快速問一下，這叫什麼？
Uh, boat row Wrong How do you get the mainsail up?
呃，船劃錯了，怎麼把主帆升起來？
Uh, rub it?
呃，擦一下？
No What do you do if I say we are coming about?
不，如果我說我們要來了，你會怎麼做？
I'd say, come again?
我想說，再來一次？
No, no, I know this one, I know this one Time's up.
不，不，我知道這個，我知道這個，時間到了。
Now you're dead And deaf!
現在你死了而且聾了！
Okay, you just go on and make your little jokey jokes But if
好吧，你繼續開你的小玩笑但是如果
you do not know what you are doing out at sea, you will
你不知道你在海上做什麼，你會
die at sea Am I getting through to you, Sailor?
死在海上 我能聯絡到你嗎，水手？
Don't just say yes.
不要只說是。
This isn't a game Joe, you could really get hurt out here Okay,
這不是遊戲，喬，你真的會在這裡受傷 好吧，
so do you want to pay attention or do you want to die?
那你是想關注還是想死？
I want to make a ship to shore call to Chandler All
我想從船到岸呼叫 Chandler All
right, I definitely taste nutmeg You do?
對了，我一定嚐過肉荳蔻的味道，你呢？
You don't?
你不這麼認為嗎？
Well, that's the difference between a professional and a layman That and
嗯，這就是專業人士和外行人的區別
arrogance Hey Hey, how was sailing?
囂張嘿嘿，航行怎麼樣？
I don't want to talk about it Now, you could at least save
我不想談論它 現在你至少可以儲存
me a whole cookie No, no, no, no, no, no Women are mean
我一整塊餅乾 不不不 女人都很卑鄙
What is that?
那是什麼？
Now the only thing that's left of my grandmother's legacy is this crumb
現在我祖母的遺產中唯一剩下的就是這個麵包屑
I wish you a long and happy marriage Hey Hey, how was it?
祝你婚姻長久幸福嘿嘿，怎麼樣？
Well, I had a great time Um, Chauncey, on the other hand I
嗯，我度過了一段美好的時光 嗯，昌西，另一方面，我
will tell the story It was going great I let him win We
會說這個故事 進展順利 我讓他贏了 我們
were bonding He even said that I could call him dad And what
他甚至說我可以叫他爸爸什麼
did he ask you, not to call him?
他有要求你不要打電話給他嗎？
Daddy All right, look, here's the story Well, we had just finished playing
爸爸 好吧，看，這是故事 好吧，我們剛剛玩完
racquetball And we were going to take a steam I walk into the
壁球 我們打算去蒸 我走進
steam room And it's really steamy So I take off my glasses And
蒸汽房而且真的很熱所以我摘下眼鏡然後
that's when it happened Guys?
就在那時，事情發生了，夥計們？
Over here Have a seat, son Hey!
兒子，坐在這裡，嘿！
Oh, Chandler, I can't believe it I know You gave my father a
哦，錢德勒，我簡直不敢相信，我知道你給了我父親一個
lap dance Why did they put so much steam in there?
膝上舞為什麼要放這麼多蒸氣進去？
Because otherwise they'd have to call it the room room Why, okay, why?
因為否則他們就得稱之為房間 為什麼，好吧，為什麼？
Why did that have to happen?
為什麼會發生這種事？
Come on, it's not that big a deal Not that big a deal
來吧，這沒什麼大不了的 沒什麼大不了的
There...
那裡...
There was touching of things Chandler, I know you wanted to bond with
錢德勒的事情很感人，我知道你想與之建立聯絡
my dad But did you really have to bond to that part?
我爸爸 但你真的必須與那部分連結在一起嗎？
Listen, I'm sure that dad doesn't care He probably thought this was really
聽著，我確信爸爸不在乎，他可能認為這真的是
funny He'll be telling this story for years I don't want him to
有趣的是，他會講這個故事很多年，我不想讓他這麼做
tell this story for years Oh, but he will He still tells the
講述這個故事很多年了哦，但他仍然會講述
story about how Monica Tried to escape from fat camp I wasn't escaping
關於莫妮卡如何試圖逃離肥胖營的故事我並沒有逃脫
Then how'd you get caught in the barbed wire?
那你是怎麼被鐵絲網困住的？
I was trying to help out a squirrel You were trying to eat
我試著幫助一隻松鼠，而你卻想吃東西
it If that is your father calling to tell this story Then the
如果那是你父親打電話來講述這個故事 那麼
marriage is off Come on Hello I'm sorry, you have the wrong number
婚姻結束了 來吧 你好，很抱歉，你的電話號碼有誤
Okay, I'll call you later, dad, I love you Bye All right, I'm
好的，我稍後再給你打電話，爸爸，我愛你再見，好吧，我
off to see your dad Whoa, whoa, aren't you a little overdressed?
去看你爸爸 哇哦，你是不是穿得太過分了？
Yeah, and you better make sure he tips you this time Look, I
是的，你最好確保這次他給你小費，聽著，我
figured I would try to convince him not to tell the story anymore
我想我會試著說服他不要再講這個故事了
And I figured the best way to do that was face to face
我認為最好的方法就是面對面
And by face, I don't mean his lap And by face, I don't
我說的臉不是指他的腿 我說的臉不是指他的腿
mean my ass Hey, are you getting Monica and Chandler an engagement present?
嘿，你要給莫妮卡和錢德勒送訂婚禮物嗎？
I don't know You know, they didn't get us anything Thank you Hey,
我不知道你知道，他們沒有給我們任何東西謝謝嘿，
hey Well, hello So when are we getting back out on the water,
嘿，你好，那我們什麼時候才能回到水面上，
matey?
馬蒂？
Well, I don't know the boat way to say this, but never Why
好吧，我不知道該怎麼說，但我從來不知道為什麼
not?
不是？
Because you're mean on the boat I was just trying to teach you
因為你在船上很刻薄我只是想教訓你
Well, lesson learned, Rachel is mean Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep I
好吧，吸取教訓，雷切爾很卑鄙是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的我
remember when she took me out on her dad's boat She wouldn't let
記得當她帶我去她爸爸的船上時她不讓
me help out at all Oh, excuse me, I wanted you to help
我完全可以幫忙哦，對不起，我想讓你幫忙
But you couldn't move your arms because you were wearing three life jackets
但你無法移動你的手臂，因為你穿著三件救生衣
You have to respect the scene Look, Joey, I'm sorry if you thought
你必須尊重這個場景 聽著，喬伊，如果你認為
that was mean But I gotta tell you something, that was not mean
那很卑鄙 但我得告訴你一件事，那並不卑鄙
Hey, my father is mean He used to yell at me all the
嘿，我父親很刻薄，他總是對我大喊大叫
time on the boat, and it was horrible I was just being a
在船上的時間，太可怕了，我只是一個
really good teacher Does a good teacher say, put down the beer pin,
真的好老師 好老師會說，放下啤酒別針，
Ed?
艾德？
Well, does a good student drink seven beers during his first lesson?
那麼，一個好學生在第一堂課時會喝七瓶啤酒嗎？
Six and a half You knocked that last one out of my hand,
六歲半 你把最後一個從我手中奪走，
remember?
記住？
Yeah, I didn't want you to get hit by the boom Well, it
是的，我不想讓你受到繁榮的打擊，好吧，它
hit me anyway And it would have hurt a lot less if I'd
不管怎樣，打我吧 如果我這麼做的話，傷害就會少很多
have finished that last beer Oh, you know what?
喝完了最後一杯啤酒哦，你知道嗎？
I'm sorry I will try to tone it down and, uh, stop yelling
抱歉，我會盡力降低音量，然後，呃，停止大喊大叫
You won't boss me around anymore?
你不會再對我發號施令了吧？
I won't boss you around And you'll be nice?
我不會對你發號施令，你會乖乖的嗎？
And I'll be nice And you'll be topless?
我會很友善，而你會赤裸上身？
Joey!
喬伊！
You want me to learn Okay, here's batch 22 Ah,
你想讓我學 好吧，這是第 22 批啊，
maybe these will taste like your grandmother's This has a little bit of
也許這些嘗起來像你祖母的
orange peel, but no nutmeg Let's give it a shot I've not made
橙皮，但沒有肉荳蔻 讓我們嘗試一下，我還沒做過
this many cookies since I was in the ninth grade What was that
從我九年級起就有這麼多餅乾 那是什麼
for, like a bake sale?
例如烘焙義賣？
No, just a Friday night These are pretty good Yeah, but not as
不，只是週五晚上 這些都不錯 是的，但不那麼好
good as batch 17 Which one was that?
與第 17 批一樣好 那是哪一批？
The ones we had right after you almost threw up Oh yeah, batch
你差點吐了之後我們吃的那些 哦是的，一批
17 was good I did not like batch 16 Okay Are there any
17 很好，我不喜歡批次 16 好的，有嗎
more from the good batch?
更多來自好批次？
Because we could just work off of those Well, yeah, I think there's
因為我們可以解決這些問題 嗯，是的，我認為有
one from batch 17 left Batch 16, 16 people, get out of the
第17批剩1批 第16批，16人，下車
way!
方式！
Okay, Joey, honey, you're doing really good All right, now I'm just going
好吧，喬伊，親愛的，你做得很好，好吧，現在我要走了
to need you to step to the port side Remember how we talked
需要你走到左舷記住我們是怎麼說的
about the port side?
關於左舷？
Oh yeah Right?
哦，是的，對嗎？
No It's left, sweetie, but that's okay, that's a tough one Why don't
不，剩下了，親愛的，但沒關係，這很難，為什麼不呢？
you just say left?
你就說左邊？
Okay, go to the left!
好的，往左邊走！
The left!
左邊！
Huh?
啊？
Just sit over there!
就坐在那裡吧！
Okay, okay, keep yelling again, see that?
好吧好吧，再喊一遍，看到了嗎？
No, no, no, no, no, very quiet, said with love, no, no Well,
不不不不不，很安靜，充滿愛意地說，不不不好吧，
you know what?
你知道嗎？
Since I'm here, I think I'm going to have me a little beer
既然我來了，我想我要喝點啤酒
on the port side See what I did there?
在左舷 看看我在那裡做了什麼？
Okay, Joey, we're luffing a little bit, so will you tighten up the
好吧，喬伊，我們有點搖擺，所以你能拉緊一點嗎？
Cunningham?
坎寧安？
All right, well, you just said a bunch of stuff I don't know,
好吧，你剛剛說了一堆我不知道的東西，
man Joey, come on, you just went over this!
夥計，喬伊，來吧，你剛剛回顧過這個！
Oh, you know, when we did that was when that bird was flying
哦，你知道，當我們這麼做的時候，那隻鳥正在飛翔
overhead with the fish in his mouth Did you see it?
頭頂上，嘴裡叼著魚，你看到了嗎？
It was gross No!
太噁心了不行！
All right, I did not see the bird, I did not see the
好吧，我沒有看到鳥，我沒有看到
fish I did not see the piece of styrofoam that was shaped like
魚 我沒有看到形狀像的泡沫塑膠
Mike Tyson I did not!
麥克泰森 我沒有！
Because I was trying to teach you how to sail a boat Which
因為我想教你如何駕船
obviously is an impossible thing to do All right, that's it, you're yelling
顯然這是一件不可能的事 好吧，就是這樣，你大喊大叫
and I don't see you taking your top off I quit!
我沒看到你脫掉上衣，我就不乾了！
What do you mean you quit?
你放棄了是什麼意思？
You can't quit!
你不能放棄！
Why not?
為什麼不呢？
Because you're not finished yet and I won't have it Greens do not
因為你還沒完成，我不會接受，綠黨不會
quit!
辭職！
Greens?
青菜？
I'm a Tribbiani and Tribbianis quit!
我是特里比亞尼，特里比亞尼退出！
Oh my God, wait, did I?
天哪，等等，是嗎？
I just said Greens don't quit, didn't I?
我剛剛說過格林不會放棄，不是嗎？
Did I just say Greens don't quit?
我剛剛說過格林不會放棄嗎？
Yes, yes!
是的，是的！
You did and you're still yelling at me!
你已經這麼做了，你還對我大吼大叫！
No, no, no, I'm not yelling at you, I'm just yelling near you
不不不，我沒有對你大喊大叫，我只是在你附近大喊大叫
Oh God, Joey, oh, I'm my father, oh my God, this is horrible
天哪，喬伊，哦，我是我的父親，天哪，這太可怕了
I've been trying so hard not to be my mother, I did not
我一直在努力不想成為我的母親，但我沒有
see this coming Oh, Joey, I'm sorry, I'm so sorry I just wanted
哦，喬伊，對不起，我很抱歉我只是想要
you to learn Hey, I did learn Really?
你來學習 嘿，我確實學會了 真的嗎？
Yeah, come on It's okay I know what a mainsail is I know
是的，來吧，沒關係，我知道主帆是什麼，我知道
to duck when the boom comes across I know port is right Left
當繁榮來臨時躲避我知道港口在右邊 左邊
Damn it What are we going to do with all these cookies?
該死的，我們要怎麼處理這些餅乾呢？
Joey You know, I bet it would actually make my grandma really happy
喬伊 你知道，我打賭這會讓我奶奶非常高興
to know that we're trying to figure out her recipe I bet she's
要知道我們正在努力找出她的食譜，我敢打賭她是
looking up at us and smiling right now Looking up?
現在抬頭看著我們微笑抬頭看？
Oh, yeah, no, she was really nice to me, but she's in hell
哦，是的，不，她對我真的很好，但她在地獄裡
for sure Well, I've tried everything, I give up I guess I'm not
好吧，我已經嘗試了一切，我放棄了，我想我不會
going to be the mom who makes the world's best chocolate chip cookies
將成為製作世界上最好的巧克力餅乾的媽媽
I do make the best duck confit with broccoli rabe Kids love that,
我確實用西蘭花拉貝做了最好的油封鴨子孩子們喜歡這個，
right?
正確的？
Oh, Phoebe, come on, isn't there any relative that would have the recipe?
哦，菲比，拜託，沒有親戚有食譜嗎？
What about your sister?
你妹妹呢？
Oh, no, no, no, I made a promise to myself that the next
哦，不，不，不，我向自己保證，下一個
time I would talk to Ursula is over my dead body And that's
我和烏蘇拉說話的時間是在我的屍體上方，那就是
not happening until October 15th, 2032 That's the day you're going to die
直到 2032 年 10 月 15 日才會發生 那一天你就會死去
See, darn it, I've got shuffleboard that day That's what you think Well,
看，該死，那天我有沙狐球，這就是你的想法好吧，
I mean, what about friends of your grandmother's?
我是說，你祖母的朋友呢？
Wouldn't they have the recipe?
他們沒有食譜嗎？
Well, you know, I may have relatives in France who would know My
嗯，你知道，我在法國可能有親戚知道我的狀況
grandmother said she got the recipe from her grandmother Nestle Toulouse What
祖母說她從她祖母雀巢圖盧茲那裡得到了食譜
was her name?
她叫什麼名字？
Nestle Toulouse Nestle Toll House?
雀巢圖盧茲 雀巢收費站？
You Americans always butcher the French language Phoebe, is this the recipe?
你們美國人總是屠殺法語菲比，這是食譜嗎？
Yes!
是的！
Oh I cannot believe that I just spent the last two days trying
哦，我不敢相信我剛剛花了兩天時間嘗試
to figure out that recipe and it was my cupboard the whole time
找出那個食譜，它一直是我的櫥櫃
I know You see, it is stuff like this which is why you're
我知道你看，就是這樣的事情，這就是為什麼你
burning it now So you understand, I'd feel a lot more comfortable if
現在就燒掉所以你明白，如果
you didn't tell people what happened You know, I'm a little embarrassed about
你沒有告訴別人發生了什麼事你知道，我有點尷尬
it I understand completely There's nothing more horrifying than embarrassing
我完全明白沒有什麼比尷尬更可怕的了
yourself in front of your in-laws As a matter of fact, when
事實上，當你在你的姻親面前
I started dating Judy, I was unemployed and her father asked me what
我開始和茱蒂約會，我失業了，她父親問我什麼
I did for a living and I told him I was a lawyer
我以此為生，我告訴他我是律師
What did you do when they found out?
他們發現後你做了什麼？
They never did So if you ever see me giving them legal advice,
他們從來沒有這樣做過 所以如果你看到我給他們法律建議
just nod along Shall we?
我們只是點頭，可以嗎？
So, I guess we wear swimsuits in here Well,
所以，我想我們在這裡穿泳衣好吧，
Joey, I hate to admit it Your way of sailing is a lot
Joey，我不願意承認你的航行方式有很多
more fun Yeah, yeah Hey, why don't you give a pull on that
更有趣 是的，是的 嘿，為什麼不嘗試呢
rope?
繩索？
Oh, we're not sailing Just pull on it All right Sandwiches!
哦，我們不航行了，就拉上它吧，三明治！
What else?
還有什麼？
Here you go Thank you Oh, wow What are you doing?
給你，謝謝你哦，哇，你在做什麼？
Sorry Don't hold it like that, you're letting all the good stuff fall
抱歉，別這樣握著，你會讓所有好東西都掉下來
out Oh Careful!
出門小心哦！
You're wasting good pastrami!
你浪費了好燻牛肉！
Oh my God I'm my dad!
天啊我是我爸爸！
I'm my dad!
我是我爸爸！